Harun Bajrić



harunbajric@protonmail.com



+387644270176



linkedin.com/in/harun-bajri%C4%87-36aa55191



https://harunbajric.xyz

Summary

Hello, I am Harun, young backend developer with lot's of experience. I have 2 years in total of working experience where I worked on few projects. My top skills are NodeJS, PHP and JavaScript. I project and develop apps that make it easier for us to live our daily lives and that make our world a better place.

Experience



PHP Developer

TešaniConnected Nov 2020 - Present (2 months +)



NodeJS developer

linije.ba Oct 2020 - Present (3 months +)

Junior Software Engineer

CodeTesani Jan 2020 - Present (1 year +)

Education



🤊 Gimnazija Musa Ćazim Ćatić

Programmer, Computer-Softwaretechnik 2018 - 2020

Skills

PHP • JavaScript • Node.js • Web Development • Writing • Programming • Poetry • Android Development • Python (Programming Language) • MySQL

Honors & Awards



Award for writing - Udruženje "Musa Ćazim Ćatić"

I was the best poet of the year 2018 in my age section.